# Joseph Oluwadara

## **BLOCKCHAIN SECURITY ENGINEER**

**PROFILE** 

I am a professional full-stack developer with experience in React, NextJS, Solidity, Rust, Cadence, NodeJS, Typescript, and other frameworks. I'm currently interested in writing and auditing high level secure solidity smart contracts.

Lagos, Nigeria +2348116361700 jsatimehin@gmail.com Github LinkedIn Twitter Website

# **SKILLS**

Solidity
EthersJS & Web3JS
Foundry & Hardhat
JavaScript & Typescript
The Graph
Rust
NextJS & React

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Blockchain Developer (Contract)

#### Astra Metaverse

September 2022 - Present

- Created an ERC 1155 token smart contract and minter
- Created a Metaverse Marketplace smart contract
- Writing APIs to connect with the smart contracts on the blockchain

# **Blockchain Developer**

#### **COLLECT WAVES**

May 2022 - December 2022

- Created & Tested an Music NFT smart Contract
- Designed an NFT market place smart contract and NFT minter
- Writing APIs to connect with the smart contracts on the blockchain
- Creation of Tokens.

# SIDE PROJECTS

## **GSP NFT COLLECTION**

A Dapp used to mint a collection of 1000 Glory Sound Prep Punks on Goerli.

#### **GSP ICO & TOKEN DROP**

A Dapp used to claim GST tokens for GSP holders, non holders can buy tokens.

#### GSP DAO

A DAO for GSP and GST holders.

### DEX

A decentralized token exchange on Goerli.

# **COMMUNITIES**

- Developer Dao Member
- Polygon Guid Lagos Member
- Code4rena
- Sherlock

# FullStack Blockchain Developer

## LivingStone Blockchain IT

January 2022 - August 2022

- Writing and testing smart contracts on the EVM compatible blockchains
- Building a UI that interacts with the blockchain with web3.js
- Created a Decentralized Exchange to swap tokens
- Interviewed and lead the daily activities of a team of Developers

# Frontend Solutions Developer

## IPI SOLUTIONS

May 2021 - February 2022

- Built a Document Management System around Microsoft Sharepoint using Angular and Typescript
- Created and Modified 3000+ Document Libraries

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE,

## **MATHEMATICS**

Federal University of Agriculture, Abeokuta

2018 - 2022